codecov.io 2018-09-29

# Codecov

> v2.0.2 - effective May 27th, 2017

Thank you for visiting Codecov.io (our “Site”). Whether you are checking out our offerings or actively using our services (collectively, the “Services”), your privacy is important to us. As such, we provide this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) to describe our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used by us.

## The Information We Collect

When you view our Site or engage with our services (the “Services”), we receive certain information, such as personal information you provide to us, information that is passively or automatically collected from you, such as anonymous information collected from your browser or device, and information to support our analysis of how you use the Services (collectively, the “Information”).

### Information You Provide to Us

While using our Site or Services, you may be asked to submit certain information so that we can answer your inquiries or provide you with our Services. In the course of these activities, we often seek to collect from you various forms of information, such as: name, e-mail address, work information (including team affiliation and repository access permissions), and credit card information.

### Information That is Passively or Automatically Collected.

While on our Site or using our Services, we may use automated means to collect various types of Information about you, your computer or other device used to access our Services. A representative, non-exhaustive list of the types of automatically collected information may include: network or Internet protocol address and type of browser you are using (e.g., Chrome, Safari, Firefox, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Microsoft Windows or Mac OS) and domains used by such providers, browser settings, and the web pages of the Site or Services you have visited. We may also use automated means to collect information relating to how you use the Services, such as product usage, your programming, and your impact on the repositories.

### Information Collected By and From Other Third Party Platforms.

By logging in to our Services through other third party platforms such as Github, you may allow us to have access to certain information in your profile. This may include your name, e-mail address, photo, gender, birthday, location, an ID associated with the applicable third party platform or social media account user files, like photos and videos, your list of friends or connections, people you follow and/or who follow you, or your posts or “likes.” Further, when you sign up for Codecov you are unequivocally permitting Codecov access to your archives on such third party platforms. Codecov does not make any adjustments to repository source code.

For a description on how other third party platforms handle your information, please refer to their respective privacy policies and terms of use, which may permit you to modify your privacy settings.

## How We Use the Information

We may use the Information to: \- Provide and communicate with you about the Services or your account with us; \- Fulfill your requests regarding the Services; \- Respond to your inquiries; \- Process your payments for access to the Services; \- Communicate with you about other products that we believe may be of interest to you; \- Enforce the legal terms (including without limitation our policies and terms of service) that govern your use of our Services, and/or for the purposes for which you provided the Information; \- Provide technical support for the Services; \- Prevent fraud or potentially illegal activities (including, without limitation, copyright infringement) on or through the Services; \- Protect the safety of our users; \- Perform analysis regarding how you use the Services or any part thereof; and \- Enhance the Services, including to build new features.

We may use “cookies” or similar technologies to associate certain of the Information with a unique identifier that then associates the Information with your device or browser. We may use cookies or similar technologies in order to enhance and personalize your experience on our Services, including to help authenticate you when you use our Services; to remember your preferences and registration information, and to present and help measure and research the effectiveness of our Services, and email communications and to customize the content and advertisements provided to you through our Services.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

### We may disclose the Information as follows:

  1. To service providers that we have engaged to perform business-related functions on our behalf. This may include service providers that: 
    * Conduct research and analytics;
    * Provide customer, technical or operational support;
    * Fulfill orders and user requests;
    * Handle payments;
    * Host our Services;
    * Maintain databases;
    * Otherwise support our Services.
  2. In response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena, a law enforcement or government agency's request or similar request.
  3. With third parties in order to investigate, prevent, or take action (in our sole discretion) regarding potentially illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to any person, us, or the Services, or violations of our policies to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Services.
  4. We may transfer some or all of your Information if we, or one of our business units, undergoes a business transition, like a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or part of our assets, or if a substantial portion of our or of a business unit’s assets is sold or merged in this way. If we believe a transfer results in a material change in the use of the Information we've collected or received about you, you will be given the opportunity to opt out of the transfer.

## Access To Your Information

Access to certain personal Information that is collected from our Services and that we maintain may be available to you. For example, if you created a password-protected account within our Service, you can access that account to review the Information you provided. You may also send an e-mail to the following e-mail address support@codecov.io to gain access to or to correct your personal Information. Please include your registration information for such service such as first name, last name and e-mail address in the request. If for some reason you wish to remove a repository, you may do so. Please contact support at support@codecov.io to remove all reports and data collected on a repository. On the off chance that you might want to terminate your account, please contact staff at support@codecov.io to erase your account data.

## Data Security

We have put in place commercially reasonable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures designed to help prevent unauthorized access, to maintain data security, and to use correctly the Information we collect online. For example, all rights to gain entrance to data and information are managed over SSL connection and all passwords are 1-way encoded, never plain text.

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of Information, we cannot assure you that Information will never be disclosed, altered or destroyed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.

## Other Privacy Matters

  1. “Do Not Track” Signals Some web browsers may transmit "do not track" signals to the websites and other online services with which the browser communicates. There is no standard that governs what, if anything, websites should do when they receive these signals. Codecov currently does not take action in response to these signals. If and when a standard for responding is established, we may revisit its policy on responding to these signals.
  2. International Transfer This Site is governed by and operated in accordance with US law. If you are located outside of the US, you are accessing this Site at your own risk. In particular, your Information will be transferred to and processed in the United States where we operate. By using this Site, you acknowledge that the data protection and other laws of other countries, such as the United States, may provide a less comprehensive or protective standard of protection than those in your country, and consent to your Information being collected, processed and transferred as set forth in this Privacy Policy and US law.
  3. California Residents—Your California Privacy Rights California’s "Shine the Light" law, Civil Code section 1798.83, requires certain businesses to respond to requests from California customers asking about the business' practices related to disclosing personal information to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. Alternately, such businesses may have in place a policy not to disclose personal information of customers to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. We have such a policy in place.
  4. Children’s Information. Our Site and Services are available on general audience websites, which are not directed to individuals under the age of thirteen (13). Codecov does not knowingly collect personal information from individuals under thirteen (13) years of age. If Codecov discovers that a child under the age of 13 has provided Codecov with personal information, Codecov will immediately delete that child's personal information from its system.
  5. Material Changes to this Privacy Policy From time to time, we may update this Privacy Policy. We will notify you about material changes by prominently posting a notice on our Site. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and with whom we share it.

## We :heart: Feedback

Any feedback on new features or suggested improvements to Codecov is awesome! Contact us with any such suggestions or any other comments or concerns. We care about your opinion and we welcome your feedback so that we can provide the most efficient and effective service as possible. https://codecov.io/support

> We value your trust in our team. We will honor our commitment to provide an awesome & secure product.
